Being invincible is my superpower
I don't mean that I am a superhero who
is out slattering feelings, cape flapping in the wind
as I zoom over the New York skyline
The truth is instead that I am a who man
of a certain age who has suddenly morphed into
invisibility.
But don't worry, this isn't going to be a
poor me story write in about a middle-aged woman
longing for her past.
That wood accomplish nothing, and I am a person
who gets things dan.
I am used to being the one everyone turns
to for answers, and the one who pretended that
I wasn't aware of the power that my looks
had as I coaxed people to do things for
me:
As you're reading this, I know that you're probably
that I probably sound like a narcissist or per harps
just a bit shallow.
I am neither of those things.
I'm a helix, and I'm skilled at getting the
results I need for any given situation.
I am the queen of manipulating or influencing people.
It's one of the hazards of my job.
I am responsible for keeping my department afloat financially,
which has not calm buy easily, or without learning
to pressure people into making quick decisions that make
them uncomfortable.
Not my problem.
As regret accomplishes nothing.
You wouldn't gnaw any of this about me, though
if you happen to notice me today sitting in
this nondescript coffee shop, I am here because it's
across the street from the hospital where I work
so I can work in peace as I finish
this grant proposal, and now I have this power
of in feasibility.
No one disturbs me while I work, which is
good because I need to submit this proposal by
tomorrow to secure our next round of funding.
If approved, this grant will bring in billions of
dollars and allow people to keep their jobs for
the next year.
So it's a big deal, and I drive under
pressure.
If you notice me though, you might assume I'm
just someone's mom getting out of the house because
I'm lonely now that my kids have moved out.
You my imagine that I have a husband who
has lost interest in me as you take note
of my thickening waistline, hair speckled with grey, and
smile lines that only my husband thinks are charming.
Neither of those assumptions would be completely wrong.
I do miss my kiss.
I might be a little lonely.
I might not, but I'm not some bored housewife
as far as my husband goes.
I'm not sure how day feels about me these
days.
We're both so busy with our jobs that I
don't think either of us takes the time to
notice the other.
We get along fine.
That's not the problem.