Out in the garden Mary sat hemming a
pocket and there came a little insect
running, oh, in such a hurry, across the
small stone table by her side.
The sewing was done, for Mary liked doing
nothing best, and she thought it would be
fun to drop her thimble over the little
ant.
Now he is in the dark, said she,
keep in mind he is only such a
little.
Mary ran away, for her mother called her,
and she forgot all about the ant under
the thimble.
There he was, running round and round and
round the dark prison, with little horns on
his head, quivering, little perfect legs bending as
beautifully as those of a racehorse, and he
was in quite as big a fright as
if he were an elephant.
Oh, you would have heard him say, if
you had been clever enough, I can't get
out, I can't get out, I shall lie
down and die.
Mary went to bed, and in the night
the rain poured, the handkerchief was soaked as
if somebody had been crying very much.
When she went out to fetch it as
soon as the sun shone, she remembered who
was under the thimble.
I wonder what he is doing, said Mary,
but when she lifted up the thimble, the
little tiny thing lay stiff and still.
Oh, did he die of being under the
thimble, said she aloud, I am afraid he
did mine.
Why did you do that, Mary, said her
father, who was close by and who had
guessed the truth.
See, he moved one of his legs.
Run to the house and fetch a wee
taste of honey from the breakfast table for
the little thing you starved.
I didn't mean to, said Mary.
She touched the honey in the spoon.