(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Once upon a time, there were four little
rabbits, and their names were Fopsie, Mopsie, Cottontail,
and Peter.
They lived with their mother in a sandbank,
underneath the root of a very big fir
tree.
Now, my dears, said old Mrs. Rabbit one
morning, you may go into the fields or
down the lane, but don't go into Mr.
McGregor's garden.
Your father had an accident there, he was
put in a pie by Mrs. McGregor.
Now, run along, and don't get into mischief,
I'm going out.
Then, old Mrs. Rabbit took a basket and
her umbrella to the baker's.
She brought a loaf of brown bread and
five currant buns.
Fopsie, Mopsie, and Cottontail, who were good little
bunnies, went down to the lane to gather
blackberries.
But Peter, who was very naughty, ran straight
away to Mr. McGregor's garden and squeezed under
the gate.
First, he ate some lettuces and some French
beans, and then he ate some radishes.
And then, feeling rather sick, he went to
look for some parsley.
But, around the end of a cucumber frame,
whom should he meet but Mr. McGregor?
Mr. McGregor was on his hands and knees,
planting out young cabbages.
But he jumped up and ran after Peter,
waving a rake and calling out, Stop thief!
Peter was most dreadfully frightened.
He rushed all over the garden, for he
had forgotten the way back to the gate.
He lost one of his shoes among the
cabbages and the other shoe amongst the potatoes.
After losing them, he ran on four legs
and went faster, so that he might have
got away altogether if he had not unfortunately
ran into a gooseberry net caught by the
large buttons on his jacket.
It was a blue jacket with brass buttons,
quite new.
Peter gave himself up for lost, shed big
tears, but his solids were overheard by some
friendly sparrows, who flew to him in great
excitement and implored him to exert himself.
Mr. McGregor came up with a sieve, which
he intended to pop upon the top of
Peter.
But Peter wriggled out just in time, leaving
his jacket behind him, and rushed into the
tool shed and jumped into a can.
It would have been a beautiful thing to
hide in if it had not had so
much water in it.
Mr. McGregor was quite sure that Peter was
somewhere in the tool shed, perhaps hidden underneath
a flower pot.
He began to turn them over carefully, looking
under each.
Presently, Peter sneezed.
Curty shoe!
Mr. McGregor was after him in no time,
and tried to put his foot upon Peter,
who jumped out of a window, upsetting three
plants.
The window was too small for Mr. McGregor,
and he was tired of running around after
Peter.
He went back to his work.
Peter sat down to rest.
He was out of breath and trembling with
fright, and he had not the least idea
which way to go.
Also, he was very damp, with sitting in
that can.
As your time you began to wander about,
going lippity-lippity, not very fast, and looking
all around.