Hello Mark D'Angry, how are you today?
Hey Brad, long day, huh?
How's the weather?
It’s okay, you know, just windy.
Cold and stormy.
Yeah, a little chilly here too, in Atlantic.
It’s about 64 degrees.
Wow, that’s warmer than here.
It's, like, 12 degrees here in Salt Water City.
That's... freezing.
Right.
No snow, just ice.
Are you doing any swimming?
No snow? That’s odd.
I was going to ask if you're doing any
skiing.
No, no skiing.
Just staying warm, you know.
That’s fair.
The kids are doing well, what are they even
into these days?
They started playing racquetball, I think?
Or was it rugby... one of those.
Oh, wow.
Didn’t know racquetball was big in Utah.
A little, the kids just play what their friends play.
It's more peer pressure than interest.
Got it.
Here in Atlantic, soccer is what kids play.
Oh, wow.
In Utah, soccer is a winter game.
Yeah, it starts in spring here.
They’re gearing up.
Right, gearing up.
Nice.
Who do you want in the Super Bowl?
Uh... Rams? I think?
That’s a choice.
Rams could do it.
I’d hope so.
Right.
I don't know most games, just those two.
As long as Patrick Mahoney isn’t in, I’m good.
Who do they play?
Uh, Baltimore?
Is it?
That sounds right.
Yeah, Baltimore.
And the Eagles... who are they against?
I don’t know.
Houston? Detroit?
Texas? Chiefs?
The Rams?
The Eagles got Rams, and Baltimore has Buffalo.
Right, Chiefs versus Texans.
Anyway, just wanted to check in.
Yeah, all good here.
Alright.
Chat next week, yeah?
Sounds good.