Rob: I'm doing okay, you know families Going crazy.
Rob: I tell you what this these snow storms are driving me nuts.
Rob: Sorry that the the family's all inside and dogs are going Sorry, hey boy take that dog out Time to talk on the phone here. Sorry Brian.
Rob: Oh, it's a loud dog. That's all I know. It's it's a I don't know a Mutt it's a mutt and it just barks at everything. It drives me nut. I Don't know Anyway, we were talking about snow storms and what what's going on with you? It's chaos over here.
Rob: Oh My gosh, I did it wasn't that like outside of a Reagan International or something like that Yeah there in Washington DC. You'd think that They're all Airspace would be the most secure with everything that's going on around there well exactly what in the world is a Helicopter Taking off outside of a an airport. I don't get it.
Rob: Oh Huh, so Why in the world you don't think that we're like under attack to you. No, I just Maybe President Trump was trying to go somewhere and they were securing the airspace.
Rob: 65 I want to say Man, that's that's a lot Can't even imagine Yeah, and was the the plane taking off or was it landing I believe it was taking off and And then I don't know. I've never heard where the helicopter was coming from or what it was doing. But Wow hmm, I Tell you what that that would be a hard I can't imagine being the person that has to make those phone calls and and visits to people to say You know, your loved ones not coming home today or ever well, I just can't even imagine being the one doing those that's Yeah, I hear you.