Being
invisible is
my
superpower. I
don't mean
that I am a
superhero who
is out
slattering
villains,
cape flapping
in the wind as I
boom over the
New York
skyline. The
truth is,
instead, that
I am a woman of a
setting age
who has
suddenly
morphed into
invisibility.
But don't
worry. This
isn't going to
be a poor me
story written
about a
middle-aged
woman longing
for her past.
That would
accomplish
nothing. And I
am a person who
gets things
done. I am used
to being the
one everyone
turns to for
answers and
the one who
pretended
that I wasn't
aware of the
power that my
looks had as I
coaxed people
to do things
for me. As
you're
reading this,
I know that I
probably
sound like a
narcissist,
or perhaps
just a bit
shallow. I am
neither of
those things.
I am a realist,
and I'm
skilled at
getting the
results I need
for any given
situation. I
am the queen of
manipulating
or
influencing
people. It's
one of the
hazards of my
job. I am
responsible
for keeping my
department
afloat
financially,
which has not
come by
easily, or
without
learning to
pressure
people into
making quick
decisions
that make them
uncomfortable.
Not my
problem, as
regret
accomplishes
nothing. You
wouldn't know
any of this
about me,
though if you
happen to
notice me
today,
sitting in
this
nondescript
coffee shop, I
am here
because it's
across the
street from
the hospital
where I work.
so I can work in
peace as I
finish this
grant
proposal. And
now I have this
power of
invisibility.
No one
disturbs me
while I work,
which is good
because I need
to submit this
proposal by
tomorrow to
secure our
next round of
funding. If
approved,
this grant
will bring in
millions of
dollars and
allow people
to keep their
jobs for the
next year. So
it's a big deal
and I strive
under
pressure. If
you notice me
though, you
might assume
I'm just
someone's mom
getting out of
the house
because I'm
lonely now
that my kids
have moved
out. You might
imagine that I
have a husband
who has lost
interest in me
as you take
note of my
thickening
waistline,
hair speckled
with gray, and
smile lines
that only my
husband
thinks are
charming.
Neither of
those
assumptions
would be
completely
wrong. I do
miss my kids. I
might be a
little
lonely. I
might not, but
I'm not submit
bored
housewife as
far as my
husband goes.
I'm not sure
how Dave feels
about me these
daze. We're
both so be easy
with our jobs
that I don't
think either
of us takes the
time to notice
the other. We
get along
vine. That's
not the
problem.